# **Guilherme Ferreira Barros**

1065 Burdett Avenue, Victoria, BC, Canada.

Email: <u>barros.guilherme21@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>GuilhermeBarros</u> Github: <u>GuilhermeBarros</u>

Personal Website: <a href="https://www.guibarros.dev">www.guibarros.dev</a> Phone: (604) 446-4407

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Graduated in Computer Science from Veiga de Almeida University in Brazil and a diploma in Web Development from Cornerstone college in Vancouver. I have over 7 years of proven experience as a software developer in electrical, financial industries, construction and law firms.

## **SKILLS**

**Frameworks, Libraries and Environments:** Node JS, ReactJS, Bootstrap, WordPress, Jquery, Ajax, Delphi, SASS, Django, On Rails, Tailwind CSS, Joomla!, Vue.js.

Languages: JavaScript, Pascal, C#, CSS, HTML, Python, Ruby, PHP, Nodejs, GoLang.

Systems and Databases: SQL, MongoDB, MariaDB, Docker, MySQL, SQLServer, FireBird.

Testing: Jest, React Testing Library, Mocha

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION	
Web Development	2021 - 2022
Cornerstone College	
Marketing Management Certificate	2019 - 2021
LCC ISS Language and Career School	
Business Administration Diploma	2017 - 2018
Arbutus College, Vancouver, Canada	
Bachelor Degree in Computer Science	2010 - 2015
Universidade Veiga de Almeida, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil	
Ruby on Rails	2014 - 2014
Caelum, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil	
Database Design	2014 - 2014
Coti Informática, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil	
IT Technical Support	2007 - 2009
Colégio e Escola Técnica Silva e Souza, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil	

### **CAREER HISTORY**

**Junior Full Stack Developer** 

Sunday Market Media, Victoria, Bc, Canada

12/2023 - 08/2024

- Built, tested and deployed scalable, highly available and modular software products using Facebook ads api and Google ads api.
- Maintain existing modules and create new features and improvements on these modules.
- Maintain Apps in React and Vue.js and create new features and bug fixing.
- Create automation for the systems
  Technologies: C#, CSS, HTML, React, Node.js, Mysql, Postgres, Vue.js, Javascript, Typescript, Node.js

## **Software Developer**

#### Cast Informática LTDA, Rio de Janeiro – Rio de Janeiro – Brazil

2015 - 2017

- Built, tested and deployed scalable, highly available and modular software products.
- Maintained existing modules and create new features and improvements on these modules.
- Strengthened developmental methodologies by introducing a code quality document.
  Technologies: C#, .net, CSS, HTML, Delphi 7, PHP, SQL Server 2008, Firebird.

Software Developer 2013 - 2015

Sanerio Engenharia – Rio de Janeiro – Rio de Janeiro – Brazil

- Collaborated with product management to design, build and test systems.
- Maintained existing modules and designed and delivered new modules.
- Contributed to the C# code base used in the automated deployment of software on multiple virtual machines.
- Developed object-oriented software, including Construction ERP.
  Technologies: C#, .net, CSS, HTML, Delphi 7, Microsoft Project, SQL Server 2008, Firebird, MySql, PHP, Wordpress, Node.js, PostgreSQL.

Programmer 2010 - 2013

K&N Comércio e Serviços em Informática – Rio de Janeiro – Brazil

- Modified existing software to correct errors, adapt to new hardware and improve performance.
- Drafted comprehensive reports to document bugs and design flaws.
- Designed and created eCommerce websites.

Technologies: CSS, HTML, Delphi 7, Delphi 5, Firebird, MySql, PHP, Wordpress, MySQL, JavaScript.

Intern 2009-2010

K&N Comércio e Serviços em Informática – Rio de Janeiro – Brazil

- Modified existing software to correct errors, adapt to new hardware and improve performance.
- Drafted comprehensive reports to document bugs and design flaws.
  Technologies: CSS, HTML, Delphi 7, Delphi 5, Firebird, MySql, PHP, Wordpress, MySQL, JavaScript.